<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>tech on /home/kiennt</title>
    <link>/blog/tags/tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tech on /home/kiennt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 11:24:04 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/blog/tags/tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Operate Etcd cluster</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/operate-etcd-cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 11:24:04 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/operate-etcd-cluster/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: This is my perspective aggregation. You can easily find these such of knowledges in the references.
 1. Context Etcd Version v3.4.0.
2. Requirements 2.1. Number of nodes  &amp;gt;= 3 nodes. A etcd cluster needs a majority of nodes, a quorum to agree on updates to the cluster state. For a cluster with n-members, quorum is (n/2)+1.  2.2. CPUs  Etcd doesn&amp;rsquo;t require a lot of CPU capacity.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Guideline</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/blog-guideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 14:40:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/blog-guideline/</guid>
      <description>In the beginning, I supposed that I&amp;rsquo;m the only one who write-up thing in this blog. But now thing was change, this blog might have multiple bloggers. So it needs a guideline to describe how to contribute.

1. How to submit a new content  Here is the source repo. Fork it &amp;amp; start writing. Create a pull request to submit your content. Make sure to create your author page.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Openstack Autoscaling New Approach</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/openstack-autoscaling-new-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 21:19:38 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/openstack-autoscaling-new-approach/</guid>
      <description>NOTE(kiennt): There is a legacy Faythe guideline. The new version is coming soon, check its repository for status.
 This guide describes how to automatically scale out your Compute instances in response to heavy system usage. By combining with Prometheus pre-defined rules that consider factors such as CPU or memory usage, you can configure OpenStack Orchestration (Heat) to add and remove additional instances automatically, when they are needed.
1. The standard OpenStack Autoscaling approach Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the standard OpenStack Autoscaling approach before goes to the new approach.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets Comment</title>
      <link>/blog/posts/lets-comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 09:47:11 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/posts/lets-comment/</guid>
      <description>Hugo ships with support for Disqus, a third-party service that provides comment and community capabilities to websites via JavaScript. But Disqus generates a shit load of page requests and heavy contents&amp;hellip; which even with the benefits that come with having Disqus in place. People just want something that can be used to post a comment, that is.
That&amp;rsquo;s why I choose a Disqus alternative - Utterances. Utterances is a lightweight comments widget built on Github issues.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
