<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on /home/kiennt</title>
    <link>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on /home/kiennt</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 11:25:36 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shanghai 2019</title>
      <link>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/shanghai-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 13:39:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/shanghai-2019/</guid>
      <description> WIP
 1. Chuẩn bị 1.2. Ứng dụng cần cài đặt 1.3. Tiền tệ 2. Di chuyển 3. Địa điểm thăm thú 4. Ăn uống 5. Chuyện bên lề 5.1. Trung Quốc và QR Code 5.2. Ngôn ngữ 5.3. Đi vệ sinh&amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Guideline</title>
      <link>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/blog-guideline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 14:40:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/blog-guideline/</guid>
      <description>In the beginning, I supposed that I&#39;m the only one who write-up thing in this blog. But now thing was change, this blog might have multiple bloggers. So it needs a guideline to describe how to contribute.
1. How to submit a new content  Here is the source repo. Fork it &amp;amp; start writing. Create a pull request to submit your content. Make sure to create your author page.  2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Openstack Autoscaling New Approach</title>
      <link>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/openstack-autoscaling-new-approach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 21:19:38 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/openstack-autoscaling-new-approach/</guid>
      <description>NOTE(kiennt): There is a legacy Faythe guideline. The new version is coming soon, check its repository for status.
 This guide describes how to automatically scale out your Compute instances in response to heavy system usage. By combining with Prometheus pre-defined rules that consider factors such as CPU or memory usage, you can configure OpenStack Orchestration (Heat) to add and remove additional instances automatically, when they are needed.
1. The standard OpenStack Autoscaling approach Let&#39;s talk about the standard OpenStack Autoscaling approach before goes to the new approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mục tiêu 2019</title>
      <link>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/target-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 23:16:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/target-2019/</guid>
      <description>Đến hẹn lại lên, thời điểm Tết đến xuân về, tui lại ngồi copy &amp;amp; paste viết mục tiêu phấn đấu cho năm mới. Tui khá là lười và dễ xao nhãng nên việc viết lên các mục tiêu năm mới đơn giản là một cách tự thúc ép bản thân. &amp;ldquo;Mày đã viết ra những điều này, cố mà làm&amp;rdquo;, kiểu vậy. À khoan, hay không viết nữa nhỉ? Lười quá&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets Comment</title>
      <link>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/lets-comment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 09:47:11 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/lets-comment/</guid>
      <description>Hugo ships with support for Disqus, a third-party service that provides comment and community capabilities to websites via JavaScript. But Disqus generates a shit load of page requests and heavy contents&amp;hellip; which even with the benefits that come with having Disqus in place. People just want something that can be used to post a comment, that is.
That&#39;s why I choose a Disqus alternative - Utterances. Utterances is a lightweight comments widget built on Github issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Viết cho tuổi 25</title>
      <link>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/viet-cho-tuoi_25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 18:20:16 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ntk148v.github.io/blog/posts/viet-cho-tuoi_25/</guid>
      <description>Hôm nay, 26/09 là sinh nhật tôi, sinh nhật lần thứ 25.
Tuổi 25, cái tuổi mà bảo trẻ con cũng không phải, mà nói trưởng thành cũng chưa hẳn, là cái độ tuổi đứng giữa ngã ba đường, có quá nhiều lối rẽ.
Tuổi 25, bắt đầu phải sống có trách nhiệm hơn vì sự lựa chọn bản thân ảnh hưởng đến những người xung quanh. Không còn có thể vứt bỏ tất cả, sống vì đam mê, theo đuổi đam mê một cách toàn tâm toàn ý.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>